paid-surveys-at-home.com 2017-12-29

# Privacy Policy - Paid Surveys at Home

IP Addresses  
We may use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our site or web server, and for the general administration of our website. Your IP address, should you decide to register and/or create a "Paid Surveys at Home" account, is also used to help prevent you from creating duplicate accounts.

Cookies  
Upon your first visit to this web site, a "cookie" is sent to your computer. A cookie is a tiny file that identifies you as a unique user. It stores personal preferences and user data, however, in no way does this tell us who you are. "Paid Surveys at Home" has two primary uses for its cookies. 

First, we use cookies to track special offers and promotions that may be presented to you as you navigate our website. This is done so that you are not presented with the same special offers and/or promotions over and over, or after you have indicated you are not interested. 

Secondly, we use cookies as part of our authenticaton system when you login to your account. If you select the "remember me" option when logging in, our site will set a cookie so that you do not have to login again the next time you visit "Paid Surveys at Home". 

While both of these activities depend on the use of a "cookie," visitors to this site always have the option of disabling cookies in their web browser. Most browsers are initially set to accept cookies. You can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or indicate when a cookie is being sent.

Information Gathering  
This web site collects online contact information in various ways, including inquiry forms, registration forms, surveys, and contests. The information collected may be used by us and our partners to send mail, email, or call the user with selected retail opportunities, or to get in touch with the user when necessary.  
Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the opt-out/modify section below.

Information Dissemination  
We may use the personal information that you supply to us and we may work with other third party businesses to bring selected retail opportunities to our members via mail, email or by phone. These businesses may include providers of direct marketing services and applications, including lookup and reference, data enhancement, suppression and validation and email marketing.

Links to Other Sites  
"Paid Surveys at Home" expects its partners, advertisers and affiliates to respect the privacy of our users. Be aware, however, that third parties, including our partners, advertisers, affiliates and other content providers accessible through our site, may have their own privacy and data collection policies and practices. For example, during your visit to our site you may link to, or view as part of a frame of content that is actually created or hosted by a third party. 

Also, via our site you may be introduced to, or be able to access, information, Web sites, features, contests or sweepstakes offered by other parties. "Paid Surveys at Home" is not responsible for the actions or policies of such third parties. You should check the applicable privacy policies of those third parties when providing information on a feature or page operated by a third party. 

Please be aware that if you voluntarily disclose Personally Identifiable Information on message boards or in chat areas, that information can be viewed publicly and can be collected and used by third parties without our knowledge and may result in unsolicited messages from other individuals or third parties. Such activities are beyond the control of "Paid Surveys at Home" and this policy.

Children Under 13  
"Paid Surveys at Home" does not knowingly collect or solicit Personally Identifiable Information from or about children under 13 except as permitted by law. If we discover we have received any information from a child under 13 in violation of this policy, we will delete that information immediately. If you believe "Paid Surveys at Home" has any information from or about anyone under 13, please contact us.

Security  
This web site has security measures in place to protect against loss, misuse and/or alteration of the information that you provide. Furthermore, we have taken every precaution technically possible to prevent any unauthorized access to the contents of this web server.

Opt-Out/Modify  
"Paid Surveys at Home" provides every user with the opportunity to opt-out of receiving future communications from us, change and modify information previously provided, or remove their information from our databases altogether.

Notice to Canada Residents  
By choosing to provide your email address to Paid Surveys at Home, you agree and consent to be contacted by or on behalf of Paid Surveys at Home at the physical address and email or phone number you provide, regardless of your status on any Do-Not-Mail or Do-Not-Call List.

Contacting "Paid Surveys at Home"  
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this web site, or your dealings with this web site, please contact us at: Paid Surveys at Home, 690 S Highway 89, Suite 200 Box 9670, Jackson, WY 83002, USA. Phone: +1-520-689-8699.

Policy Changes  
"Paid Surveys at Home" reserves the right to change this privacy policy at any time. 

This Privacy Policy was last revised on December 23, 2016.
